Hi, friends. This is Tekema. I am coming to you on video today sharing some tragic news.
My sister, Kimberly, my youngest sister, my only sister, Kimberly's best friend, Ajaka A.J. Owens,
mother of four, was shot and killed in Ocala, Florida. Those of you who know me know my family
lives in Ocala, has for many years. And apparently on Friday night, Ajaka, who actually resides in
the apartment my sister used to live in, her children were playing in the field on the side
of this woman's house. After the children came in in the evening, they came in after playing,
Ajaka's oldest son went back outside to retrieve his iPad that he left and found out that the
neighbor had picked it up. And as he asked for it back, the neighbor called him a n***h and also
refused to give him back the iPad and picked up a pair of rollerblades and hit him with them.
Of course, he went inside and let his mother know what occurred. And his mother went over,
Ajaka went over to the neighbor's house to ask for the iPad back and for hitting her children. And
as she approached the house, she was shot and killed. She was shot through the door and she died
at the scene. This occurred on Friday in Ocala, Florida. And as of today, this woman has yet to be
arrested. And today at three o'clock Eastern time, there will be a press conference that is going to
be held at the new St. John Missionary Baptist Church in Ocala, Florida. And we are asking that
folks share the information about Ajaka's killing far and wide with your networks. We have also put
together a GoFundMe to support burial expenses as well as legal expenses and expenses of taking care
of the children. You can find the link to that in my bio. So again, thank you for your support.
I'm asking you now to share this video far and wide with anyone you know in the media,
any celebrities that can bring attention to this matter. Share it with everyone you know. This is
clearly a matter of folks being emboldened by staying your ground. And it has resulted in four
children losing their mother. So I am asking you personally to share this with your networks,
share this with your friends, your colleagues in media and social justice, but we need justice
for AJ. Thank you. Please check out my, please check out my bio for a link to the GoFundMe page. Thank you.